(this["webpackJsonpquiz-app-starter"]=this["webpackJsonpquiz-app-starter"]||[]).push([[0],{10:function(e,t,r){"use strict";r.r(t);var s=r(0),a=r.n(s),n=r(3),o=r.n(n),i=(r(9),r(1));function c(){var e=[{questionText:"Where would I like to go on a vacation with you?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Mountains",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Beach",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Some Village",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"No vacation. Just stay at home and relax",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Who is CEO of Tesla?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Jeff Bezos",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Elon Musk",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Bill Gates",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Tony Stark",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Which date night would appeal me the most?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Going out for drinks",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"A fancy meal out",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Ordering Pizza, Watching movie at home and having sex",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Going to the theatre",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Out of these which meal I would prefer the most?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Subway Sandwich",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Burger",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Tacos",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Salad",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Which vacation destination would I pick?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Hawaii",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Disney World",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Spain",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Paris",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Who is my most favorite superhero?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Superman",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Hanuman",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Batman",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Ironman",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"As a child what do I wanted to become?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Doctor",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Lawyer",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"President of India",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Judge",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Out of these which is the thing do I love doing the most to you in bed?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Cuddle",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Kiss",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Tickle",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Sleep with my hand on your stomach",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Which facial feature of yours I love the most?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Your cute Nose",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Sexy Eyes",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Luscious Lips",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Cute Smile",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Which activity I want to do with you?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Paint together",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Karaoke",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Cook together",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Play Dota",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"What was the first movie we saw together?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Love Aaj Kal",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Me Before You",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Bhoot",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Shubh Mangal Zyada Saavdhan",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"What was the first movie we saw together?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Love Aaj Kal",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Me Before You",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Bhoot",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Shubh Mangal Zyada Saavdhan",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Other than 69 which other sexual position I wanna do with you the most?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Doggystyle",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Cowgirl",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"The Standing Ovation",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Spooning",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"What kind of traveler am I?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Planner, who likes to set an itnerary for everything",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Spontaneous",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"I prefer to stay in hotel and sleep",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"The movie which I want to watch with you when we would be together",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Sarfarosh",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Andaaz Apna Apna",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Nayak: The Real Hero",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Bahubali: The Beginning and The Conclusion",isCorrect:!1}]}],t=Object(s.useState)(0),r=Object(i.a)(t,2),n=r[0],o=r[1],c=Object(s.useState)(!1),w=Object(i.a)(c,2),h=w[0],u=w[1],T=Object(s.useState)(0),x=Object(i.a)(T,2),l=x[0],C=x[1];return a.a.createElement("div",{className:"app"},h?a.a.createElement("div",{className:"score-section"},"You scored ",l," out of ",e.length):a.a.createElement(a.a.Fragment,null,a.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-section"},a.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-count"},a.a.createElement("span",null,"Question ",n+1),"/",e.length),a.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-text"},e[n].questionText)),a.a.createElement("div",{className:"answer-section"},e[n].answerOptions.map((function(t){return a.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(){return function(t){t&&C(l+1);var r=n+1;r<e.length?o(r):u(!0)}(t.isCorrect)}},t.answerText)})))))}o.a.render(a.a.createElement(a.a.StrictMode,null,a.a.createElement(c,null)),document.getElementById("root"))},4:function(e,t,r){e.exports=r(10)},9:function(e,t,r){}},[[4,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.9b27ae33.chunk.js.map